Friends, I am the one who bought this 50 lakh policy.
The money paid to buy it is now
It has decreased a lot. Because the government
The 18% GST has been reduced to zero.
So you've been online like this lately
GST has been reduced from sales.
They buy a lot of things outside, right?
Okay, and give me some time.
Give me a policy if you don't get married.
Should I take it if I have a married wife and children?
Should you take a policy and what should your parents do?
Should I take a policy for my wife's pregnancy?
What policy should I take if I am going?
For those who are already at home,
Such major health for adults
What policy should you take if there are problems?
You should go to the hospital immediately.
How many lakhs of lakhs will it cost to take them away?
This health insurance bill is being billed
You can pay money through.
For this, a total of 31 in India
Screening health insurance companies
If I did, I wouldn't even touch these.
I put aside what I wanted. All this
Again from insurance companies
Even in each insurance company
How many policies are there to go inside?
Look at their features and note their data.
Since then, these six companies
Taking and staying related to them
See all important information.
For comparison in tabular forms,
How many days does our team have to show you?
Our intention is to make every effort.
The only good policy for you and your family
Whatever feels right to you is yours.
That's all you have to select.
Now, this is what I'm going to show you.
Even the data in the box goes like this
Collected from each one
Data is now all you need, so much effort and time.
There is no need to put it. With in few
Minutes are all over this website.
You can display the information in the form of boxes like this.
You will see. How much money for how many lakhs?
Start from the point where you want to tie it.
Compare all the features available.
When good service goes to our client
Where can I get good service with good
Features Best Value for Money These Three
Add a good health insurance
If you want to take the policy for your family
What is the ending of today's video for you?
Clarity comes. I agree with that 100%.
I will write. Why are you so confident?
I mean, for the last two months.
Work on these and complete them.
Look at all the brochures and see what they contain.
All futures are noted down.
List all of these out.
Compare them and see how they are.
Ask and find out practically.
What are the claims for in hospitals?
Coming. What has the most complaints?
There are. IRDI Documents
Verify the amount and submit this
I present to you the video.
I'm bringing it. A good one for your family.
Our intention is to have a policy. Video
Watch until the end. Like if you like it.
But my request is definitely yours.
Everyone in Friends and Family
Share with someone. It's their mistake.
Taking the wrong policy without knowing what the data is
There is a possibility. Neglecting to take that
With this video, I am sending a message to their family.
A good health insurance policy
Those you helped take
Will be. Let's start the video. This
Our efforts related to video
In the coming time, you will receive this data in the form of
The efforts we put in when we see
If you want to encourage us, definitely.
Like the video. Already Health
Do you have insurance?
If so, what policy did you take?
How much premium is being paid for it?
Have you ever been to a client?
What is the experience? If possible, comment it.
Will you tell me in the section, health is important for many people?
For opinions on insurance
Listening to something on social media somewhere
There are, right? Whether it's positive or negative.
However, the answers you give to it
They have genuine information.
Say whatever you feel. If it's negative, say it.
Negative is positive but positive is negative
Make sure you have insurance.
What kind of experience will it be?
Share in the comments section. Now
Let's start the video. I am health.
Why should I take out insurance?
I have a problem, a health problem.
If you say it, it won't come in my body, in my body.
I think I also got it scanned, something like that.
The issue will come out, but our bodies will
Moving forward while adjusting
There will be. When our body tells us
It says when you say it's not because of you.
Then go to the hospital and get tested.
This condition has existed since time immemorial.
You must have shown regular health
Should have checked. Now this
There is a problem, this needs to be done.
Imagine if they said it would cost lakhs.
Is that money in my bank account?
Because I'm not prepared for this.
I am not prepared for a health problem.
What should I do with my children? Where should I go?
I have to go, what should I buy? EMI like that.
I am prepared for these.
I am not prepared for this. Now
I will withdraw money from my bank account for this.
If I take money, my wife, my children, my
Everything that is future related
Dreams with this one hospital bill
What should I do if I get distracted?
When does this body problem occur?
I don't know, so I'll see you in the future.
But my wife and my children have no
Even if you have a health problem, it will cost you up to this many lakhs.
I don't want to touch the money in my bank.
Health insurance is what you take. Now
Tell me who should have this.
No matter how big the bill is, I
I'm not afraid, I have money in the bank.
Health insurance for those who want it
They might think that it's not necessary.
It's good to have millions at some point.
Instead of putting 1000, if it is not in the hundred, 1000 2000
Health insurance in lakhs
What's there to take if it comes?
When you definitely want to use it
Wouldn't it be better to take it, even if you have money?
Let's just say they left it at that.
10 lakhs 20 lakhs 50 lakhs in the bank
For those who thought we wouldn't have this
But if you don't have health insurance, that day
One day will come. Without listening to this,
They pushed it to the point and then left.
Then you will understand with negligence.
Please help me with the family's finances.
Neglecting the road condition
I request that no one pull.
One health for every family
Must have insurance. Good health
Must have insurance. How is it now?
Let's talk. What you need
Important information I am first.
I will tell you. How much money does it cost?
If you take a male, how many male plus female?
How many male and female plus ones?
How much does it cost to take out a policy with children?
A 10 lakh health insurance
Suppose I am an individual and I
My wife and my children individually
Taken individually, each person
There is a health insurance of 10 lakhs, right?
If everyone takes out a policy together,
What is the benefit of a 10 lakh policy for everyone?
If we take it individually, it will be
For those who think it's a profit, 30
Years Male 30 Years Female Children
Two children are 10 years old.
Let's say they are a boy and a girl.
How can they take it one by one?
If you take it, there will be premiums included.
How premiums are due for intake
I will explain to you that they change.
I will. And where does all this data come from?
I am taking this policy at the bazaar.
Online aggregator in which you
Not just buying insurance
Renewal is also possible. This
Why did I show up on the platform?
What I mean by that is, you compare yourself to your heart's content.
Compare which ones are the best.
Choose the policy you like and click on it.
Can be taken. I am a term insurance.
But, health insurance is not included in this.
I got it. Description Comment
There will be a link in the section, click on it.
First you will come to this page. Now
25% extra for making GST zero
Are you saying they are giving discounts? All that aside?
Let's keep it. But did you see here, self, wife,
Son, Daughter, Father, Mother, Grandfather,
Grandmother, Father-in-law, Mother-in-law
You can only take it for them. So
If you are self-employed
Want to take an individual
I am putting the policy age at 30 years.
If you put 25 and 22, the premium will be significantly reduced.
Let's talk logically.
The majority of them are over 30 years old.
So 30 years
I'm taking it, I'm taking it, city.
If you put many important cities
Sometimes insurance premiums
Grow. Because there is a big
There are hospitals. Big big
They will be charged a big bill at the hospital.
Are you the same towns or villages?
Suppose you put some premiums.
Decrease. And put towns and villages
Can I get treatment in the city?
They think so. Zonal Health Insurance
There are policies. So which zone are you in?
But the treatment is in that zone.
It should be done. Imagine going into the city.
You can save 10% or 20% on your total bill.
80% health insurance if you pay close attention
As the saying goes, "Whatever you do, you will get what you pay for."
Where to get treatment
Put the area there.
Just put the city. Also to your parents.
Even if you are in the city, put your city
Don't take it to your parents. Your parents
Treatment is done in the village itself.
That's where their hospital network is located.
If you want, give them that area.
Decreases. So, okay, I put the city forward.
I'm going. Your name, your mobile number.
If they ask, they will give health problems.
They ask if there are any. No for now.
I am ticking that. For parents too
I'll tell you, the policies are there, I'm S.
Tick ​​and tell us what problems you have.
We need health insurance immediately.
I will also tell you what to use. First cover
I'm coming closer. I have 25 lakhs.
If it's 99 lakhs from here, I'll give 50 lakhs.
I want to take the cover. Because
Husband and wife and children in a family
The cost of living today when there are so many people
No, we are taking health.
Insurance Next 10 20 years
Even at 30 years old, we are healthy.
We will be carrying insurance.
So how much will prices go up in those days?
Because it's a hospital bill
We have a big cover from now on.
Must be taken. Why take it now 10
I will take it every year for 20 years.
I'll get it later. Then I will raise it.
So we've got a problem in the meantime.
Let's say we need to increase our coverage.
Health insurance company
You may not agree. And remember 10
Your premium will increase from Rs. 1 lakh to Rs. 20 lakh.
It won't be double. 20 lakh to 40
Double your policy if you increase it to lakhs
It's over. It won't be triple. Somewhat
It will keep growing. So ideally
Start with a minimum of 20 lakhs.
Do it. If I were you, I would have 50 lakhs.
I will believe what my family says. So 50
The locks are close. Now you
All the policies have arrived, right? Many policies.
All of this has arrived. Of all of this, I have this.
I only start companies.
I will show you pricing related.
So now how much does this man get for this 50 lakhs?
Take care to take the ultimate
Isn't that the ultimate care?
So far, these six companies I mentioned
To the main plans that are related
Here you can see how much it will cost.
You can see it in the table. From here you can
The information comes in the tables themselves. So
I took him to the policy bazaar again.
How would you describe each one?
They can analyze what is best and what is not.
I will show it along with the percentage.
Look, give me a few minutes.
See this Male 50 Locks Policy
Taking Hyderabad location
What problems did I put in?
Which companies, brands, and policy names?
Here is the data on how much premium will be charged.
You will have it. Right, she's married now.
Done. R already has a wife.
There is. He had a doubt. He is alone.
Should I take my wife separately? He is alone.
This is the premium if he takes his wife separately.
Maybe they'll build it again, but now
Male due to taking both of them together
50 lakhs coverage for both male and female
Two people are covered by health insurance
How much does the insurance premium cost?
That's also here on the screen for you.
I am putting it. This is important, watch this.
How much is it if you take the comparison only male?
The premium is male plus female.
How much premium was paid while taking it?
What percentage of the extra was spent?
Here you will find the data that has increased.
A man has not grown 100%, has he?
It takes two people to take it.
That's because it didn't increase 100% for what it took.
I love my wife, my children, and my children too.
I will add it so that my children can eat it together.
Because not everyone gets sick at the same time, right?
That policy when someone gets sick
We will use 50 lakhs cover if someone gets sick.
We use it when it falls. Restoration
We will take whatever benefits we can get. What?
What is the Restoration Restoration Benefit?
I think I'm a problem.
Think I used it like 50 locks in the policy
Let's say I used a 20 lock.
Then my wife and children will be there.
I have another problem related to this.
But again it's 50
That's what it means to refill for lakhs.
But in the year, the terms and
There are conditions I am restoration.
I will tell you when I say benefit 50
Suppose there is a lock cover plus restoration.
Can a family be brave?
Taken together instead of individually
We can only take it 40% closer.
Growing only close to 40 to 50%
It grows and covers both. But
If you look closely, Manipal is more in signal.
It will be. Manipal above all
If you add another person to Signal
It takes. So should we take it individually?
Should I take two together? I'll take two.
I think we should take it together. Wife and
Husband adds two more children
If you do one girl one boy two 1010
If you add the years of age, how much is it now?
See if the premium is charged. Husband
How much is the premium when you have a wife?
With the addition of two children, the total is four.
How much did the premium increase after becoming a People?
What is the percentage of rice?
You can see. See also here
Manipal Signal is the most
It has grown. So individual person
Manipal Sig when you want to take it
Separate. Two people are being added, four people are added.
The Manipal Sig is different. Everything else
Same category. So this is a clarification.
Did Manipal Signa add two?
If you are doing it, add four people.
How much higher is the premium than the rest of these companies?
It increases more and this gives you
There needs to be another clarification. Individual
By taking it together instead of taking it separately
We pay less premium. Because
100 100% isn't increasing, right?
Do you think we are practical?
Here's another thing we're learning.
It should also be said. Here I am, wife.
Add only husband and children.
I did it. Parents were not added. In
I didn't add the loss, I added my aunt and uncle.
Didn't. Grandmother Grandfather
No ads. What happens in this case is this.
We also set tables like this.
You can go. In fact, those tables too
I have them. Butt length seen
Then I put it aside.
The conclusion I would like to give there is
It doesn't matter what your age is, anytime.
The group with the highest age is the group that
The premium for the entire policy is paid by that person.
Of a person who is of high age.
It changes depending on the condition. So
Wife, husband, and children as one group
Stay. Mother, Father, Inlaws
Create a group of your choice.
Their ages are all similar.
To the grandfather and grandmother
If there are any other conditions, they
Put it in another group. No
They are all of similar ages.
Everyone's conditions are similar.
If you want, put them all in a separate group.
But these children are wife and
Mix it with the group where the husband is staying.
Don't do it. So individual or family
Floater means going on a family floater.
Better. Take a good cover and make a big one.
Restoration benefit by removing the cover
If you want to put it individually
This is better than taking it, ideally.
How much cover should we take individually?
Should I take it or should I take a family float?
Who is taking the family float?
Clarity that it should be put as a group
But you came here, my friends.
There is data, have you seen this policy bazaar?
Go into it and make plans for each one.
Considering all the prices,
Reformat it as a table and make it
Also, so many companies are related.
Look at each one again 10 more
Plans, these plans, all of them.
Husband took that money and put it away.
Looking at the wife, looking at the children
Comparing them again, you can see this:
This is not the next one in the form of tables.
How long will it take to bring it back?
And efforts will prevail.
They think we put too much in.
All I ask of you is a like.
Make your own opinion.
Comment and most importantly
Please pass the information on to everyone you know.
Share. Share the video
Try putting it in the status.
At least one family is a good policy.
They will come in the coming times.
Avoiding a big hospital bill
That merit will go to you. Financially
Many families have one hospital bill.
They are overwhelmed by the hospital bill. Every
One personal health for one household
Must have insurance. Now these
Let's compare. With these you have a
Clarity comes. An individual year
What big problems will arise? He will tell his
Which of these policies should the wife buy for her children?
Do you want to talk now? I
Think here will reveal why I am
I took HDFC Ergo and it's the same for everyone.
It can be said that it is not suitable for everyone.
Why is that also the next five or six?
I will make you understand in minutes.
I will tell you. Friends, now I
The data that is going to be presented to you is literal.
Imagine it. This description
Policy Bazaar in the comments section
Click the link and see our details.
How many insurance companies can fill the form?
From time to time, each insurance
How many policies are there in the company?
Go inside and see what their features are.
Take note of their data and from there
Taking these six companies and their
The whole thing about being related is important.
See the information in a tabular format.
For comparison in forms, you
How many days of effort does our team have to show?
Our intention is to remain silent.
What is a good policy for you and your family?
Whatever feels right to you is yours.
That's all you have to select.
Now, this is what I'm going to show you.
The data of the box also goes like this
Collected from each one
Data is now all you need, so much effort and time.
No need to put it in, just in case.
Minutes are all over this website.
You can see the information in the form of boxes like this
You will see. First Why I'm Going With
HDFC Ergo is because of the interest
Climate ratio of the last three years
See average 97% 79% 89% in the industry
In the standard R industry
They beat the average. ₹1
If you are collecting, it will be close to ₹86.
Giving. And in my favorite companies
In second place is IICI Lombard.
There is. That's why we always wish them health.
While making insurance videos
I even put on shorts, didn't I?
When I asked what to buy, which companies did I choose?
I say. IICI Lumberyard RicI
Elevate HDFC Ergo Incred Climb
The ratio is very high. Its meaning
I just said that ₹1 rupees will be collected.
If they do, how much will they pay back?
Are you doing it? How many rupees?
Are you doing it? HDFC Ergo is 86.
If they are IIC Lambada, then 83 is your place.
58care 59star
73 tata age 81 aditya birla 68 so therefore
Always between 80 and 85%
Incurred Claim Ratio
I select what is there.
I wanted to do it. Because Health
Insurance is not about the features
What did they put in, what colors did they put on?
Health insurance is not based on that.
There is. You want to climb.
You get a claim when you go.
It's important to do so without being harassed.
When I think about it, I
It is visible. What is the problem with HDFC Ergo?
If you take it, will you give it to me no matter what I say?
Don't claim, look at this 10,000 claims
HDFC Ergo Loseven is on the way.
There are complaints against IRDI.
They won't give us 10,000 kisa as a claim.
Let's see the rest. IICI Lonine
There are. Aditya has 22. In Manipal
There are 25 in Care, 36 in Neeva, 43 in Neeva.
There are. So obviously the number of
Complaints are also less.
Ergo, what is the recorded climb ratio?
These two complaints are minimal for me.
I felt a rupee because I saw it.
Let's put more, a good cover will come recently.
New riders added in 2025 as
So I took it. But we
When you want to take it to your mother,
I will take it or not, but for my brother.
But when you want to take it,
I'm ICI for them, whether they take it or not.
I'll go to Elevate because...
Interesting riders staying like that
They are not requirements for me.
What do you think, riders?
When you explain
It will be known. So number of complaints
And the recorded claim ratio is the same.
How is the room? Is there a room rent limit?
There should be no rent limit and whatever.
Whether it is or not, the data is also for you.
I'm putting it in front of the screen here.
Restoration benefit unlimited times
Unlimited times in everything
It's called restoration, but it's not like that.
Don't look at it simply from their side.
Insurance from the policy bazaar side
Will the expert call be unlimited?
There is a restoration, but what are its classes?
Tell me the same problem 10 times.
I'll go, will it be covered?
If you want to go to the problems,
Explain to us what the conditions are.
Ask for the Restoration Benefit
If you want to take it as a policy related
But unlimited number of times
Restoration for any illness
It's a good thing, ergo.
Only once a year in
Our policy is the only one we have spent on.
We will get refilled again. Free and
Will they cover the post-hospital expenses?
How many days are insurance companies?
You will have that data here.
90 to 180 days maximum means we have to wait for surgery.
Surgery completed 90 days before departure
Expenses for the next 180 days
They will bear it. Surgery is the only
It's not about having surgery, it's about what happens after it.
It's also a lot, isn't it? What are 90 days?
180 days and what are 60 days 180 days
It will be. The more it is, the better.
Good. With these consultation doctors you
Instead of going directly, go through
Consult Electronic Means Online
Do you have the option to do so? Is that a majority?
It's in everything. One Aditya Birla
OPD cover except in Active One Max
Did you go to the doctor that day?
If he prescribes medicines together
Let's go to the doctor, shall we?
We'll pay the money, right? It means there's a majority.
It is not inbuilt in any way. Rider
It would be like that. We need to add that.
Here's what to look for when taking out a policy
It looks like Raiders. There you have it.
It says OPD cover.
Will the premium increase if I do it? Where is it?
The more money you show, the more premium you get.
Increases. Through it you can get to the hospital
When I went to the hospital, it wasn't surgery, it was just like that.
He went to the doctor and left.
You can also get money for that through this cover.
It's coming, but that's my personal opinion.
It's not so much a requirement as an OPD cover.
It's because he took us to the hospital.
If you go to the doctor for a check-up,
The premium that increases money here is not worth it to me.
Doesn't seem like a benefit. So even now
See, we have an impact in millions.
We will be. Health to save it
I need to get insurance but they don't.
We have a few small biscuits.
These riders seem to be throwing
In other countries, both locally and globally
Is there an option for you to show it too?
The majority of them are not in the hefc ergo
Is there a co-payment in Neiva Bupa?
You are a certain percentage of the bill.
The insurance company is left with nothing.
It's final. 20% co-payment for a bill of one lakh rupees
Suppose you took 20% of your
If you pay 20,000, you will pay 80,000.
The insurance company is responsible. What do we need?
The entire bill is the insurance company's.
To pay, you have to take a co-payment.
The premium will be reduced by. You are the year
The one who pays for the year, the one who pays for the month, the one who pays for the six months
The premium will decrease. So some people are
Then let's build some ourselves.
Let's reduce while building.
They think so. But I think it's strong.
I object, don't take it that way. That
HDFC Ergo does not have a co-payment for you.
There is no option. Not in IICI but Manipal
But you can do it as an option.
Can be taken. If you select it, you
The premium will decrease. Anger is called payment.
Suppose you are selecting IIC.
See in Co-payment as a writer
It is visible. Once you add it, you
The premium will decrease. But in the rest
It doesn't exist in the sky. And deductible like
Now here's how much you can deduct.
You'll see what's being put on as soon as it's put on.
The premium you pay has decreased. There
Let's say there is as much as they are putting in.
Assume you are paying 50,000 maximum.
You will pay 50,000 rupees in your hands.
It goes from. What goes after that?
The entire insurance company takes care of it.
That's it. This is good for older people.
It's expensive. Deductible for the elderly
If you put 50,000 there, it will be very big.
The total amount of money is decreasing. So
I will give you whatever you want here.
They say the premium will also decrease there.
Almost a 60 to 70% match for that.
Logic is like that when it happens.
You can go, don't go, angry payment.
Go for the deductible if you need it.
I don't even need that, it's premium.
I think we should build a little more.
And consumable cover is included in most insurances.
Get a non-consumable cover here
Every insurance company has it.
Consumable cover must be a must
Look at every single insurance company.
It has a consumable cover inside, but
It has a name by that name
Want to be added to Like Care Supreme?
Look, it's called Rider Climb Shield.
It should be added like that. Specific
Illness means slow growing diseases.
Are all these slow-growing diseases?
How many years of waiting do they have?
There is a period, which means two years.
It's close. The majority of everything is the same.
When we get into the Where's Manipal signal
But it is health for the elderly.
Especially for those with problems
It means that it exists. Senior Citizens
That is the policy to look for. The original of it
For specific illness but not for
Existing but like initial 30 days
But it doesn't have any of those. Happily
Age and they can use it.
So even in what was shown yesterday
Even in shorts, for those who are older than you
If there are health problems, these two are the ones
See below what Manipal said.
There is a signal. Param Paidi IC Elevate IC
How to use Elevate Senior
I will show it to the citizens.
This is not something that is shown by putting boxes in it.
I'll show you how to go directly.
Show the policy and pre-existing
Diseases are mostly common to all three.
It will be years. That means we already have it.
If there is a problem, it will be close to three years.
Wait. So we have health insurance.
This slow after two years of taking
We have health only with growing diseases.
Insurance works. Same to us.
Problems that already exist
That person is something that exists to us.
The person who took it has a heart attack and liver disease.
There must be some problem with the kidneys.
Imagine if he said it when you took it.
He should wait three years, majority.
Among them, Manipal Signal is the only one
There's no waiting. Even we can do it.
Riders are also welcome in the rest of Lamba.
You can add or subtract, I'll tell you.
Let me show you, we are still senior citizens.
Didn't go near. And you are my uncle.
It depends on the plan you take.
Gold was taken in the Gold Plan.
For pre-existing diseases, if any
You have to wait four years for a diamond like this
Three years if taking platinum titanium
We have to wait after taking it.
Existing problems
Depending on the insurance you want to show.
And wellness benefits keep you healthy
Fit and healthy activities
You are doing what you are supposed to do.
You will be charged on the insurance premium.
Medicines may be discounted, but
Treatments but anything additional you
You always have money to invest.
Which policy can offer discounts?
Here are the wellness benefits
I am putting the screen in front of you, Aditya.
Up to 100% premium for you at Birla
They say it's hard, but it's very tough.
Mostly it's very, very tough to make it happen.
Everything else is also related to a
There will be a procedure. We are just us.
They think they're walking.
That doesn't mean you have to install certain apps.
We must do certain things for them.
Because it's only five if you prove it.
This is not something we can take away so easily.
But still, there are programs in these.
So that's a premium for you, you're further along.
On what to spend money on
They provide us with discounts.
As if doing. Now in these six companies
What interesting feature do you
I'll see if it attracts. Very
Some features are interesting.
This is the reason I said I am the best.
I thought it was for you.
Maybe not. Attracts you
The features may be different. Take a look.
First HDFC Ergo will start with 2X
There will be cover from day one. Optima
Another word for secure is super secure.
There is a plan. Actually I took it.
If it doesn't have to be done for three years
To that. Both of these are secure and super.
The difference between secure and secure is that
Only 2x comes in Super Secure 3x
Comes. Let's say you have a cover of 25 lakhs.
I think they took it, maybe in a secure place.
50 lakhs cover from the first day
It is said that it will happen. 75 in Super Secure
They say you will get lakhs of cover.
The second thing is that even if you claim, you claim.
Even if you don't, year after year, you will be fine.
Your sum is close to 50% of what you took.
It keeps getting added to Azure. That means two
How much have you taken over the years?
Let's say you earn 25 lakhs in the first year.
Suppose you have taken a policy.
You paid for years and left.
If so, it would have been doubled. And
Somehow they are giving 2x from the first.
So take a secure plan.
They have three years.
The policy sum assured taken is three times
It will be. 2x already giving 50
50% in the next two years
It is being doubled. Total 3x
If we take Super Secure, that means three
Three years of planning
It will only be activated for you if you select it.
It will be automatically super secure.
You will get three times in the beginning.
Then another 100%, 50% in the first year.
50% total in second year renewal
Four Times Assured You of Your Equal
Growing. And beyond this
What are the interesting features of HDFC Ergo?
Are you in, meaning recently?
They brought in some new riders.
Because it's the usual stuff in everything.
I'm neglecting it.
We need to talk about IICI Lambad.
Very interesting features Power Booster
That would be it. Once you have a power booster
If you take it, your sum is assured every year.
The policy you have taken is 100%
100% will continue to grow. Unlimited
That's it. Took a policy of 10 lakhs
This is what a power booster has added. Every
Year it keeps growing by 100 100%
There will be. And have a good CIBIL score
They even give them a discount.
They give. And another one called Infinite Care
There will be an interesting feature. You can do this.
If you add it, it will be your entire lifetime.
Once a year is not good.
You have to think. How big is once in a lifetime?
Even if it's a bill, it's a scam. Your policy
Let there be no cover. How much are you?
It doesn't matter how big the bill is.
It's a once in a lifetime experience. A small
Confidence is always a big thing.
This will be used if a problem arises.
This is some time back for ISIS.
The policy brought is interesting.
It will be. There is nothing wrong with taking it either.
And they have unlimited sum assured.
There is also. That means that this is the limit.
No. You can take it as much as you want.
Policy. Next Aditya Birla Active
There is one called the Chronic Care Rider.
This is underlined for senior citizens.
Must do. This is an ad for senior citizens.
If you have a chronic condition,
Problems are already there.
All these existing diseases are also excluded.
What is the waiting period in years?
This without a waiting period of years
Taking insurance to the hospital
It is useful for you to use. So
If you add a chronic care rider,
You have asthma since day one.
Whatever the problems are, wait.
Can you show me? Super Credit
This is a facility that you can add if you want.
Regardless of whether you claim or not,
Your cover is 100% of the policy you have taken.
It keeps increasing and increasing, up to 500%.
Multiple again in Manipal Signal too
There are variants. The best is the best.
In fact, this is a service for senior citizens.
I made a video, we already have it on our YouTube.
Please note that it will be on the channel. Theirs
There is no waiting period. What else?
There are no waiting periods. Those who are aged
People with health problems should
If you take out a policy, you will face many problems.
From the very beginning, you
Start using insurance.
You can. And along with this, multiple
There will be riders. These riders who live here
They are all very interesting riders.
Manipal signal for those who are also so-aged
That would be good. And for those who are old.
Jump start in IICI Lombard too
This rider jump start is one of those things.
And also for pre-existing diseases
Rider who reduces waiting period
There is also. So that's why I'm saying this, right?
I have a lot of health problems.
I think there are, I'll go to heaven.
Or now regarding ICICI Bank
Present that jump start but not pre
It reduces existing diseases but
I will have done it. That's why it's best for someone.
Why isn't it better for someone else?
Conditions are different, your conditions are different.
Too many problems depending on the problems
There are, you don't know what it is.
If you don't know what to do, Manipal Sign
Param, you have clarity, pre-existing.
Jump to know what diseases are there
Rider is able to start.
Able to add IIC Elevate
So I think it's a bit of an interesting policy.
Even if the money is reduced, it means value for money.
Money is my problem now.
No, for future problems.
I'll take care of it now.
If you think there's nothing left, I'll take it.
What I took because of HACCP Go
You don't have it right, there are still some left.
What's left is Aditya Billa active?
Also not a bad chronic care rider
If you post an ad, you'll get a job there.
What's left, take care, grandpa?
I don't prefer them as much. Butt a lot
People have less money than that.
There is an advantage if there are more features.
They say there will be more. Butt
Complaints are more frequent.
My climb ratio is also low. Butt
I will also tell you the features they have.
Next Care Supreme Plan Related
An interesting feature is that
SuperNCB, if you add this, no.
Claim Bonus is added at 100% every year.
She would go to Seven Times.
Next this is instant cover for you
There are pre-existing diseases.
Imagine taking this and this insurance.
You can make it work for you.
So, wait another three years.
Must wait two years
Not so, instant cover pre
Existing diseases
Used to remove the waiting period
Since it's a cover, any problems?
Those who stay care.
Instant cover when you want to take it
You should definitely add him as a rider.
Finally, you can lock the clock.
It will be. That means my age is 32 now.
I think I took it, you idiot.
Then I saw this Locked the Clock ad.
I think I'll do it until I claim it.
Health if age increases due to age
Insurance premiums are increasing.
It does not change, it changes due to inflation.
The premium is not the same. Premium
It is increasing because of inflation.
The premium will not increase due to my age. When?
The second one is until I climb
Borderless coverage means not only
Climb anywhere in India, anywhere.
Go and show me if you have a problem.
That's what it means to say. This is maternity coverage.
Maternity is a miracle plan under
What comes into play is not only
Pregnancy Even IVF But Surrogacy
But all this is still this maternity motherhood
Many related things are covered here.
Will be. And Booster Plus Benefit
Whatever you use, some assured particular
The thing is not used. That's for you next year.
That's how it's carried. 10 times you
It will continue to come until the policy cover increases.
With you and disease management rider
There are already health problems.
Three years, two years, I
There should be no waiting period.
I think so. This rider should be added.
Wright is right in all these policies.
Do you understand the interesting features now?
Let's talk. No problem, two.
Three years of slow growing for me.
Even if diseases occur, immediately next
I haven't used a big policy for two years.
When asked to have fewer complaints
Who are the people who make the most claims?
Then I will go to HHS.
No, I have a problem, a health problem.
There is. Complaints are few and unrecorded.
The higher the claim ratio, the better.
Riders are giving me benefits. IicI
I'll go to Elevate. I have there.
It seemed like the premiums were high.
Think sometimes there is less
There are also higher premiums.
There are fewer cares, less in you.
There are many complaints. So are they.
Don't give it to everyone else, you mean?
40 complaints out of 10,000 50 complaints
The remaining 9,950 is still a claim, as if it was given.
The ratio is somewhat low. Those two
It's okay to take the concerns as they are.
What are the benefits of them?
Take care. Who is Manipal Signa Param for?
Aged People and Those Who Have Already
There are problems. Still waiting
Periods, these riders don't want all of this.
If you want to start directly
That's it. That's why it has a higher premium.
Some. And you understand it more clearly.
What do senior citizens need to be able to do?
If you add riders, all of these
What kind of benefit will there be?
Directly into the policy market
I will take it and explain it to you.
Let me explain to you live data.
I will. Watch Father and Mother here
I got it. Didn't take any selfies.
If I want to take it to my mom and dad
Select Father and Mother and proceed.
I'm going to enter their age.
I'm giving both of them 50 years of age.
So enter 50 years and click continue.
Where do you live? You live in Hyderabad.
I put that. Your favorite area
I'm clicking continue.
If we put our name and number, we will get it.
Call them and ask about the policy.
To help them give confirmation
There will be. Do they have any problems?
Are there any problems here?
I am putting it. Even if you have problems
Even if they are, let's go inside.
You can sort it out. Because
Everyone has their own problem. So
So individually, the problems here
Not selected. What's the problem?
I am putting it. You have a problem.
Even if you put it in, most of the plans are for you.
These will appear. So almost a
We see 63 plans, but 63
There is no need to watch. We care about you, Bupa.
Everything you want will be there. So I am a star.
Not taken into consideration. Even
We talked to Aditya Billa, HHC.
Ergo, we talked about ICI Elevate.
We talked about and Manipal
We talked about Signa. So these are for us.
Everything you could want is here.
So let's start with the Manipal signal.
For the aged people anytime
Plans available when you want to take them
You should keep all this in mind once.
Compare premiums, note that.
Let's finalize it later. Manipal
There are two in the signal. It will be better.
There will be a limit. Maternity for you in Uttama
That said, there are benefits. So if you
Wife or pregnancy plan
Stay strong while you're doing it. No parents
They want to go with their related
No waiting for you from the first.
You mean you don't want to have a period?
First of all, it's a zero waiting period for you.
That's it. What you already have is existing.
The problems that exist are specific.
Diseases, but whatever they are, from day one
You will be covered from the first day of purchase.
It will be. But what about three years?
But you have to put the riders on.
Make it specific or slow for 30 days.
Growing Disease lasts for two years
You can reduce it to 30 days.
But if you have old people
They have problems as parents.
There are many existing issues.
If you want, just go with Sarvaparam.
Click and you will love you here.
Does it take a customized plan?
How much do you want to give them?
You can buy your policy by taking the premium.
Can be taken. After that, here you go.
Bold writers appear. Just read.
What is a surplus benefit?
They say it all, Air.
They say ambulance, like any issue.
If you are direct, you are fast.
In a helicopter to carry
Take you from here to another place.
They say they will do it. I don't need all this.
Opinion. So take a look at the deductible.
I said it was a very close deductible.
If you put it in, you will lose money.
Now the deductible is Rs. 1,00,000.
I think I paid a premium.
The amount being paid is 38,000, so it should be reduced by 17,000.
They say. So look, I applied for 38,000.
It decreased from 17,000 to 21,000. Its
What does it mean now the deductible is 1,000,000?
What does it mean to put?
10 lakh insurance taken
I have been to the hospital at least once a year.
How many times a year do you go?
I am going to Maxim, I have one lakh rupees.
I will put it in my hand. 9 lakhs is enough.
They put it on. But how much do I owe it?
I reduced it to 17,000 per year.
I have reduced it. So if you think it's worth it
I don't need to keep it.
When it comes, I will definitely
If they have to give it, that's okay, voluntary anger.
I wouldn't suggest it if it's anger.
I wouldn't suggest taking it. And
24 months for specific diseases
Or will you wait two years and 30?
Days Initial Waiting Period
If you put it in, you get a premium.
There is no need to reduce it further.
We should not have a waiting period.
I'll take it, isn't this just a policy?
I'm coming back. So one by one first.
Let's get out of the stock, take care.
Back into the Ultimate Care Plan in
If you're going, come to the Raiders below you.
View More Riders View Pre
Will it reduce existing diseases?
Will you reduce the waiting period?
The default is three years, but one
If you want an extra premium of 4000 per year
It is called a bandage. Then instead of three years
Just wait one year and you will get this
Take the policy and go happily.
Treatment can be done. Apart from that
There are some problems. If
Diabetes, thyroid, heart,
Hypertension, hyperlipidemia, asthma
All this is not even one year, but 30 days later.
You should give it to your parents right away.
That insurance will be valid for 30 days from now.
These problems should be useful to them.
If you think it exists, you should add it.
It's called instant cover. Annual Health
If you want to check it out, this is the ad.
Must do. No need for a butt. OPD Care
It is said that four times general
Anyone else go to the physician?
When you go for consultations,
If you want to reemboss, it is called OPD care.
Outpatient consultations are called
All of these are not requirements. This
Pre-existing diseases instant
The cover is what you should focus on the most.
So take care of this. Same as Niva Bupa
What we've seen so far is the Aspire
Gold Annamata Yes Per Gold Plus Ya
This is So Click Customize This
I'm doing it for my parents so...
Come here and see Disease Management
Is it called gold? It's been around since day one.
Cover for diabetes and hypertension
Should I cover both of them? Should I cover only one?
Do you want to do it? It's too much to cover for both of you.
Yes. What if the father has diabetes?
They only care about the father, the mother is the only one.
Diabetes is considered a single mother.
Or both of them have it, both of them
If you have two types of BP and diabetes,
They put two of them on each side like this.
Even for the elderly, you have a deductible.
Premium savings are good when you put it in.
It looks like it's happening, but watch out.
The amount you pay as a deductible is the amount you pay for the year.
How many times have you been to the hospital?
If you're going for that much money, you're the best.
Pay. We at Aditya Birla also
What plan did you see? Active One Next
I'm clicking Customize.
Coming down, reduction in riders
Waiting for pre-existing diseases
A period is three years.
You can reduce it to one year.
I told you about chronic care from day one.
Chronic problems related to you
Your father and mother, whoever they are, both of them.
Kante selected both of them.
Enter their details.
If you like them, you will get data.
I will say I will enter. See
Whatever problems they have, they are Day One.
You can put it so that it covers from the start.
That's it. What issues do they have?
Three Three Problems
You take each one and give them a day.
So that it can be applied to them from the beginning.
You can put it. So this is chronic care.
This is an ad for you by. Sohechac
Interesting things like that, if you're a goalie
I didn't say anything because I didn't have anything. IicI
It is in the elevator. So customize the element
Click on the plan to jump start.
That's what it says here, Infinite Kar, all of this.
We talked about jump start, didn't we?
Jump Start is a chronic condition that you have.
What problems do you declare?
I think you clicked on the ad here, Father.
And they ask Mother again.
I'll ask you for details.
They ask all the problems.
If you have problems, start from 31 days.
From that time, even after one month,
All problems are covered by insurance.
Will be covered. Whatever is pre-existing
Even if there are diseases, it is three years.
One year from the waiting period
We also do this for the waiting period.
You can bring it. Is it clear now?
Maternity Pregnancy Pregnancy
Thinking that the baby is not delivered?
Is normal delivery or cesarean section the only option?
No, in terms of IVF or egg freezing
Whether in terms of surrogacy or adoption
However, in many ways, this maternity
Coverage varies from company to company.
Gives. Maternity related
If you want to take health insurance
It's about giving policies. What is the company?
I'll even tell you the name. Star Health
Even in the very interesting thing though
There is a maternity hospital in But Star Health
Personally, I am grateful to my family.
I don't want to take it, so I
It's not discussed, it should be included.
I didn't say that. Individually, already.
For those of you who are taking Star Health
Hope you have a good experience, Obvious.
You can go with that, but personally I
I didn't go for it at that level. So
What are the policy names and their waiting periods?
How much less is the new one visible?
Months are actually a different matter.
There's a thing called fast forward.
There is an option. Usually 25000
But in fast forward we have 75,000
Even close to us in terms of maternity
Benefit is available. HDFC Ergo is a
The waiting period is two years.
Buy it two years in advance if you want to use it.
Should be. We have a maximum of 2 lakhs.
They give. IicI Lombard The Two
Maximum waiting period in years
One lakh rupees is 10% of our sum.
Assured, whichever is higher, is the max.
The maximum maternity benefit we receive.
Aditya Birla 40,000 AMO Normal Delivery
They give 60,000 for a cesarean section. Three
You will have to wait for years. Butt
We can reduce it. And if
Is anyone at Aditya Birla looking for maternity leave?
If you are planning, also see this policy
Interesting policy Manipal Lo Max 5
It's worth up to lakhs. 20% off our price
The insured amount is up to Rs. 5 lakh. Three
There is a waiting period of years.
If not, and new born means new
Already expenses for a newborn baby
I think it's all started.
Any expenses for them after birth
I think they have arrived, will they cover everything?
Children covered and vaccinated
There will be vaccinations after birth, right?
They are not covered in all of them, they are separate.
Riders should be taken. So what's up?
You can also find out what kind of coverage is available here.
I'm putting it in front of the screen. Hope you
Clarity has come in terms of maternity as well.
Calculated properly
I want to go. How much do we actually spend?
We are putting this on maternity leave. How much?
We are spending money, but what benefit do we get?
Proper calculations must be made.
If you have any questions related to this, please contact us.
If you want a dedicated video in terms of
Add up all the calculations and you have a
If you want to make a video, I will. Already
It's going to be too long, isn't it? More details.
You think it's better to go into detail.
Pregnancy until the necessary information is available
I have provided it in terms of veterinary care. And
Finally want to take NRS
Hope these three policies work for you.
Will be. Who is an NRI? Who is an Indian?
Why does India have citizenship in a country other than India?
No, the one here should go somewhere else.
Worked, working, working.
Anyone, be it OCI or RNRI
The person who left India is someone else.
Health here while staying in the country
When taking ins again anytime
They come here to use it, don't they?
Health insurance or any holidays?
Any health problem that comes up
If you show it there, you will get money.
Come here because it will be more.
Health insurance, even if you want to show it off
They will get work in India. These three
Why do I say NRI?
There will be a discount. Nawabs 15%
They give. Which one is better now?
I say. GST has been removed. GST
Even if you go, we'll get a 15% discount this new year.
It comes from nearby. And HDFC Ergo
Get a 40% discount from nearby. But
The class they taught was Let's
Say you are paying a premium of ₹10,000.
40% discount means you save ₹6,000
Can be tied. Taken in India
An NRI pays 6000 more. But what year?
But if you come to India and use it,
Do you use health insurance?
Then only that year you
The remaining premium must be paid in full.
They should build it the way they build it.
The discount you have been given until then
Don't ask. They will only ask that year. And
25% discount for you on IIC Elevate
There will be. So when you take it, you are an NRI.
If you are taken in the category, you will get that
There are benefits. SoARIS those three
Check the policies once. Hope you
Total in terms of insurance
All the information is clearly understood.
What is the major question that comes to your mind now?
Mistakes I should not make while taking
Don't lie, right?
Tell it like it is, even if you lie.
If you think that, remember that it is true.
You need to get fixed. Scene in the movie
They are in their house as if they have something that is not there.
We also try to convince ourselves, don't we?
It should be fixed, but as far as I know
No one can be like that until now. Near something
Tell the truth because you will be caught.
There will be a free look period. You are the policy.
Online for all these days taken
Get 30 days of free look
There will be a period. 15 if taken offline
There will be a free look period for days. That
Do you have any policy issues within
Even if it is, you can send it back and get your money back.
You can withdraw the money. Lie
Without further ado, you all are in the free look period.
Check and renew from time to time
You should not use that insurance.
That health insurance, as mentioned
Put it in and it's taken from you.
Tell your friends at home too.
Tell me too. What is health insurance?
No. If something happens tomorrow morning
If they knew we had this
They mentioned it in the hospital.
Will do. And what do you need in the climb?
If there are issues, this is right, but they are still
If you are creating any issues
Just remember that your side is at fault.
If not, you have a problem at that point.
You can get your money back even if it's being created.
It means there is nothing wrong with your side of the fence.
Your money will be returned to you with interest.
You have to pay it back with interest.
How did they get our money back?
The related subscriber is also live.
Case study I will explain to you here
I did it. How to fight is actually simple.
You can do it online or offline.
You can also do it online. How online
This can also be done offline.
It's in the video. If you add this again
It would be more. So this video description
I will give it in the comment section. Health
This is for everyone who has taken out insurance.
The video should be clear. How
Can we fight? Is it necessary to have education?
No, it is not necessary to have income to have a business.
What are the things that need to be done and what are not necessary?
Income tax returns are also not required.
Because it is for every family.
It should be so and it's important.
So the government also made GST zero.
Understand what you did.
I watched this video to give importance.
Don't watch any more videos later. This video
Comment on the description after watching.
Click the link in the section and your
Fill in the details and you and your family will be able to
Add everything related to
How much is it, including the details?
It costs money. How much money does it cost?
Please check once.
Do it yourself, you won't see it.
This neglect is due to not knowing the cause.
You still need health insurance.
Those who have already taken it are left without it.
How much money do you save at the hospital?
That's your experience.
Negative or positive in the comment section
Share it with us too.
You will see. They will decide after seeing it.
And friends again before closing
I'm saying it again, GST prices.
Less than what I took now
You see, it comes very rarely.
"Be slow, who's watching?"
To increase the prices that GST has reduced again
You have the idea that you should start taking
Whatever you have, take it now.
Don't neglect your parents.
If someone has a health problem, it
Your bank account is yours again.
Do you understand that the fall is an impact?
Whose responsibility is it for all of them?
No matter what happens to them, you can't just leave them like that.
They will definitely spend money on them.
One healthy thought for everyone
If you pay for insurance tomorrow
What is happening to you, lakhs of hospital bills?
The bank will not be emptied.
This small gift to everyone who earns
Many people are careless without awareness.
Doing one major health financially
They are constantly on the road with problems. Please
Don't make that mistake. For every family
There must be health insurance. Taking
They will take this information.
Share with your friends and family.
Another interesting one, hoping they will do it.
I'll see you again with the video.
Until then, take care, Jai Hind.